

Roberto Carlos Martínez Loredo

Web Developer

Tampico, México

roberto.martinez.loredo@gmail.com

+52 833-303-52-69

Portfolio: https://robertocarlos.netlify.app/ro berto-carlos/index.html

https://github.com/rocamalo

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- TYPESCRIPT
- ANGULAR
- IONIC (Mobile Development)
- NODEJS WITH EXPRESS
- **NESTJS**
- MYSQL
- POSTGRESQL
- MONGODB

Languages

Spanish · Native

English · Advanced

I am a passionated engineer with 5 years of experience in IT and 3 years as a web developer, committed to developing quality software, focused on frontend technologies like Angular with knowledge and experience on back-end, open to learning other types of technologies and interested only on remote iobs.

Work History

Web developer **Aztlansoft**

México Jan. 2021- Current

- Assigned to project Beelinguapp, a company which main product is a Learning Language Mobile Application for Android/IOS, as a Fullstack Developer using technologies such as Html, Css, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Java with Play Framework and MySql, in charge of development of the API, internal tools and the main webpage.
- Assigned to an Oil & Gas client as a Frontend Developer, to fully focus on the creation of components, made by the designers, using Angular with PrimeNg and occasionally support backend developers with NestJs.
- Maintenance of a delivery application for local business made with Ionic and Java with Play Framework for the
- Design and develop from scratch a web page for searching car parts using Svelte with Bootstrap.
- Develop and maintain web projects using frontend and backend technologies such as Angular, Ionic, Svelte, Bootstrap, PrimeNg, Material, Java with Play Framework, NestJs, MySql, PostgreSQL and SQL Server.

Web developer & IT engineer

Eseasa Offshore

México

May. 2018 - Dec. 2020

• Maintenance of network, servers and webpages of the company.

• Development of applications for internal use according to the clients needs using technologies such as Html, Css, Javascript, Angular, Ionic, NodeJs with Express and MySql.

• Give technical support remote and on site to all employees and foreign clients of the company.

Junior IT engineer MN del Golfo

México Jan. 2017 - Apr. 2018 • Technical support remote and on site to all employees.

- Server administrator responsible of the backups and security, in charge of creating SQL Queries to retrieve data from the SQL Servers.
- Maintenance of php and mysal based code internal applications.

Education

2016 Bachelor's degree in computer systems engineering Instituto Tecnológico de Ciudad Madero.